export default data = [
  {
      question: "The ______ is so strong today that my hair keeps blowing in the air",
      options: ["rain","snow","sun","wind"],
      correct_option: "wind"
  },
  {
      question: "When the baby cried, Mr. Wu ______ in the kitchen and did not hear it",
      options: ["cooked","was cooking","has cooked","is going to cook"],
      correct_option: "was cooking"
  },
  {
      question: "I don’t have any money with me because I ______ my wallet this morning",
      options: ["had lost","would lose","lost","was losing"],
      correct_option: "lost"
  },
  {
      question: "You need not only good luck but also hard work to become a ______ baseball player",
      options: ["young","successful","happy","friendly"],
      correct_option: "successful"
  },
  {
      question: "The woman who lives next door to Ken is a ______ to him. They have never met and he doesn’t even know her name",
      options: ["daughter","friend","stranger","teacher"],
      correct_option: "stranger"
  },
  {
      question: "With the new bus line, it is much more ______ for Fanny to go to school. It saves her a lot of time now",
      options: ["useful","possible","interesting","convenient"],
      correct_option: "convenient"
  },
  {
      question: "Dad: Have you brushed your teeth yet? Ann: No, but I ______ before I go to bed",
      options: ["haven’t","have","won’t","will"],
      correct_option: "will"
  },
  {
      question: "Alice: Do you know ______ Grandma is going to visit us? Willy: It’s next week. She told me on the phone. And we’ll take her to the national park",
      options: ["where","when","whether","why"],
      correct_option: "when"
  },
  {
      question: "It took the police lots of time ______ who entered Liu’s house and killed her one year ago",
      options: ["and found out","find out","finding out","to find out"],
      correct_option: "to find out"
  },
  {
      question: "Many famous people visit this restaurant. Popular singers like A-mei and Jay Chou ______ here with their friends",
      options: ["to be often seen","often seen","are often seen","and are often seen"],
      correct_option: "are often seen"
  },
  {
      question: "The factory has been throwing trash into the river for years. Now ______ must be taken to stop this",
      options: ["action","chances","exercise","notes"],
      correct_option: "action"
  },
  {
      question: "The beach party tonight ______ the end of our summer vacation. Tomorrow we are all going back home and getting ready for school",
      options: ["changes","marks","passes","saves"],
      correct_option: "marks"
  },
  {
      question: "Anyone who reads Loren’s business plan will quickly see some serious problems in it, or ______ feel something is not right",
      options: ["at least","even","in fact","still"],
      correct_option: "at least"
  },
  {
      question: "I’ve wanted to read The Diary of a Young Girl for months, ______ today I finally borrowed the book from the library",
      options: ["and","since","so","until"],
      correct_option: "and"
  },
]
